jarvee.com 2019-06-07

# JARVEE privacy policy - the best social media automation software around

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which **JARVEE** collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [http://jarvee.com](http://jarvee.com/) website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by **JARVEE**.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

All account information that you use within our software ( Jarvee) is kept locally on your computer and we never have access to it in any way or form. Everything you do there is completely private and up to you and it’s your responsibility to keep it safe.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site uses “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

An objection to the use of cookies used for online marketing purposes can be declared for many of the services, especially in the case of tracking, via the US site <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> or the EU site <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/>.

**How we use collected information**

**JARVEE** collects and uses Users’ personal information for the following purposes:

  * _To improve our Site_  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * _To improve customer service_  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * _To process transactions_  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * _To send periodic emails_  
The email address Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
  * Provide, improve, test, and monitor the effectiveness of our Service.
  * Develop and test new products and features.
  * Diagnose or fix technology problems.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**What is your data retention policy?**

We will make a good faith effort to:

  * Retain server logs containing the IP address of all requests to this server no more than 90 days.
  * Retain the IP addresses associated with registered users and their posts no more than 5 years.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party websites**

Users may find content on our Site that links to third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA ([Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Children%27s_Online_Privacy_Protection_Act)), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our site and not to information collected offline.

**Does Jarvee comply with the EU General Data Protection Regulation?**

Jarvee respects privacy rights under [Regulation (EU) 2016/679, the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation](http://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/?uri=uriserv:OJ.L_.2016.119.01.0001.01.ENG) (GDPR). Information that GDPR requires Jarvee to give can be found throughout this privacy notice.

**How can I change or erase data about me?**

You can change your account data at any time by visiting the profile settings page for your account. Closing your account will remove all data about you that is stored on our servers, you will also have to unsubscribe from our mailing list separately if you don’t wish to hear from us anymore.

In case you cannot access your profile page anymore you can also send us an email using the [contact form](https://jarvee.com/contact/) and we’ll close your account for you.

**How can I contact Jarvee about privacy?**

You can send questions and complaints to using our [contact form](https://jarvee.com/contact/) and someone from our legal department will help you out.

For complaints under GDPR more generally, European Union users may lodge complaints with their local data protection supervisory authorities.

**Third-Party Sites and technology partners**

  * [Akismet](https://akismet.com/) is used for spam prevention on the Jarvee site. You can see their privacy policy here <https://automattic.com/privacy/>
  * [Google Analytics](https://analytics.google.com/) – compiles visitors statistics, you can opt out using a [browser extension](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Here is their privacy policy : <https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/>
  * [Wpxhosting](https://wpxhosting.com/) is used as a hosting provider for the Jarvee wordpress site. Here’s their privacy policy: <https://wpxhosting.com/page/privacy-policy/>
  * [Paypal](https://www.paypal.com/) is used as our payment processor. Their privacy policy: <https://www.paypal.com/ro/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>
  * [Google adwords](http://adwords.google.com/) is used as a marketing platform. Check out their privacy here: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

**Changes to this privacy policy**

**JARVEE** has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

This version of Jarvee’s privacy questions and answers took effect May 25, 2018.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of [this policy](http://jarvee.com/privacy-policy/) and our [terms of service](http://jarvee.com/terms-of-service/). If you do not agree to them, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please [contact us here](http://jarvee.com/contact/).
